Inventory of the Norman Allderdice Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Series I
  - Daily Worker Publishing Company, Chicago, Illinois, undated. (Folder 18: 48)
    Catalogue
  - The Dailys, undated. (Folder 18: 49)
    Group letter
  - Dan Smoot Report, 1950s. (Folder 18: 50)
  - Dannenhower, Washington, Mrs., Knoxville, Tennessee, undated. (Folder 18: 51)
    Poster
  - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1952. (Box-folder 19: 1)
    Printed matter and proclamation
  - Day Care Centers, undated. (Folder 19: 2)
  - Dayton Public Service League, Dayton, Ohio, 1944. (Folder 19: 3)
  - Debs, Eugene V., undated. (Folder 19: 4)
  - Defenders, Inc.
    - Kansas City, Missouri, 1960s. (Folder 19: 5)
      Form letter and poster
    - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, undated. (Folder 19: 6)
    - Wichita, Kansas, 1950s. (Folder 19: 7)
      Brochures, form letter, message, and miscellany
  - Defenders of American Education, Tucson, Arizona, 1956-1957. (Folder 19: 8)
    Articles, reports, and related materials
  - Defenders of State Sovereignty and Individual Liberties, Arlington Chapter, Virginia, undated. (Folder 19: 9)
  - Defenders of the American Constitution, Washington, D.C., 1955-1961. (Folder 19: 10)
  - Defenders of the Christian Faith, Kansas City, Missouri, 1950s-1960s. (Folder 19: 11)
    Printed matter and miscellany
  - Defenders of the Constitution of the United States, 1935.; See also box 25 (Folder 19: 12)
    Brochure and photocopy of the Great Seal.
  - Defenders of the U.S.A. Republic, 1962. (Folder 19: 13)
    Statements
  - Defenders of 3 against HUAC, Washington, D.C., 1964. (Folder 19: 14)
  - Defense Committee, 1970. (Folder 19: 15)
  - Demand MacArthur, Dallas, Texas, 1952. (Folder 19: 16)
  - Democracy, 1943-1958. (Folder 19: 17)
    Clipping, printed matter, statement, and related materials
  - Democracy Advisory Council, Washington, D.C., 1959. (Folder 19: 18)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1960-1964. (Folder 19: 19)
    Brochure, form letter, and printed matter
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, New York, 1970s. (Folder 19: 20)
  - Demonstrations, 1966. (Folder 19: 21)
    Brochure, clipping, flyer, newsletter, notice of a meeting, proposal, and miscellany
  - Denton, John, undated. (Folder 19: 22-23)
    Clipping and flyer
  - Depression, 1934. (Folder 19: 24)
  - The Detroit Council of Applied Religion, Detroit, Michigan, 1947. (Folder 19: 25)
    Form letter and invitation
  - Dewey, John, 1954. (Folder 19: 26)
    Record of activities
  - Devin-Adair Company, 1955, 1962. (Folder 19: 27)
    Flyer, letter, and miscellany
  - Dies, Martin, 1953, 1966. (Folder 19: 28)
  - Dilling, Elizabeth, 1954. (Folder 19: 29)
  - Dilworth, Nelson S., undated. (Folder 19: 30)
    Memorial
  - Dirty Dozen Campaign, undated. (Folder 19: 31)
  - Disarmament, 1961. (Folder 19: 32)
    Printed matter, report, and related materials
  - Disarmament News and Views, 1972. (Folder 19: 33)
  - "Dixon, Jeane ...," Anderson, Jack, undated. (Folder 19: 34)
  - Dodge House, Washington, D.C., 1969. (Folder 19: 35)
    Agenda of a meeting
  - Do You Know Company, 1956. (Folder 19: 36)
  - Dollars for Defense, undated. (Folder 19: 37)
    List of contributors
  - Douglas MacArthur Society, 1968. (Folder 19: 38)
    Outline and printed matter
  - Draft laws, undated. (Folder 19: 39)
  - Dreyfus case, 1899. (Folder 19: 40)
  - "Dru, Philip ...," Matthews, J. B., and Gerald B. Winrod, undated. (Folder 19: 41)
  - Drug abuse
    - Alcohol, 1973-1976. (Folder 19: 42)
      Articles, printed matter, and miscellany
    - Barbiturates, 1974. (Folder 19: 43)
      Brochure and printed matter
    - Book reviews, 1971. (Folder 19: 44)
    - Clinics and hospitals, 1971-1974. (Folder 19: 45)
      Articles, clippings, list of free clinics, memorandum, minutes of meeting, printed matter, and program
    - Cocaine, 1977. (Folder 19: 46)
      Articles and printed matter
    - Community Organization for Drug Abuse Control (CODAC), 1970. (Folder 19: 47)
      Article, clipping, letter, note, plan, organizational chart, and statement
    - Darvon (Propoxyphene), 1974. (Folder 19: 48)
    - Depressants, 1974. (Folder 19: 49)
      Articles, brochure, and miscellany
    - Drug identification, 1970. (Folder 19: 50)
      Guide
    - Education, 1969-1972. (Box-folder 20: 1)
      Agenda of a meeting, article, brochure, clipping, letter to the editor, flyer, printed matter, schedule, and related materials
    - Side effects, 1973-1974. (Folder 20: 2)
    - Foreign countries, 1971-1975. (Folder 20: 3)
    - General, folder 1, 1970-1971. (Folder 20: 4)
      Article, journal, and reference book
    - General, folder 2, 1969-1970. (Folder 20: 5)
      Articles and pamphlets, including "Drugs: For and Against," "Drug Dependence: A Guide for Physicians," and "Federal Source Book: Answers to the Most Frequently Asked Questions about Drug Abuse"
    - General, folder 3, 1968-1971. (Folder 20: 6)
      Articles, brochure, fact sheets, journals, and pamphlets
    - General, folder 4, 1956-1975. (Folder 20: 7)
      Articles, clipping, letters, memorandum, notes, petition, and statement
    - General, folder 5, 1969-1973. (Folder 20: 8)
      Articles, letter, and statement
    - General, folder 6, 1970-1977. (Box-folder 21: 1)
      Articles, brochure, newsletter, pamphlet, and printed matter
    - General, folder 7, 1971-1977. (Folder 21: 2)
      Articles, clipping, journal, and memoranda
    - General, folder 8, 1971-1978. (Folder 21: 3)
      Articles, clipping, and printed matter
    - Glue sniffing, 1972-1975. (Folder 21: 4)
      Articles and miscellany
    - Hallucinogens, LSD, etc., 1971-1976. (Folder 21: 5)
      Articles, brochure, clipping, printed matter, and related materials
    - Heroin, folder 1, 1971-1974. (Folder 21: 6)
      Articles, clippings, flyer, and related materials
    - Heroin, folder 2, 1971-1977. (Folder 21: 7)
      Articles, flyer, and paper
    - Law enforcement, 1971. (Folder 21: 8)
    - Legislation, 1971. (Folder 21: 9)
      Articles, clipping, letter, and related materials
    - Infant addiction, 1972-1978. (Folder 21: 10)
    - Marijuana (general), 1970-1978. (Folder 21: 11-12)
      Articles, brochure, clipping, printed matter, and miscellany
    - Marijuana (medical), 1971-1977. (Folder 21: 13)
    - Marijuana (legalization), 1971-1976. (Folder 21: 14)
      Pamphlet, printed matter, and miscellany
    - Methadone, folder 1, 1970-1977. (Box-folder 22: 1)
      Articles, bulletin, newsletter, printed matter, and miscellany
    - Methadone, folder 2, 1970-1971. (Folder 22: 2)
      Articles, clipping, newsletter, and printed matter
    - Methadone, folder 3, 1971-1977. (Folder 22: 3)
      Articles, newsletter, printed matter, and statement
    - Military, 1971-1973. (Folder 22: 4)
    - Narcan and other narcotic blocking agents, 1976-1977. (Folder 22: 5)
      Articles, clipping, printed matter, and miscellany
    - Opiates, 1972-1975. (Folder 22: 6)
      Articles, clipping, flyer, and printed matter
    - Overdose, 1970-1977. (Folder 22: 7)
      Articles, clipping, and report
    - PP, Angel Dust and other articles, 1973-1977. (Folder 22: 8)
      Includes clipping, printed matter, and report
    - Street Jargon, undated. (Folder 22: 9)
      Pamphlet and miscellany
    - Physicians, 1971-1977. (Folder 22: 10)
    - Qualudes (Methaqualone), ludes, quackers, 1972-1974. (Folder 22: 11)
    - Sports, 1973-1975. (Folder 22: 12)
    - Stimulants, 1971-1975. (Folder 22: 13)
      Articles, brochure, clipping, journal, and printed matter
    - Suppliers, 1970-1976. (Folder 22: 14)
      Article, clipping, and letter
    - Tobacco, 1971-1978. (Folder 22: 15)
      Articles, printed matter, statement, and related materials
    - Plants, herbs (not including marijuana), 1975-1977. (Folder 22: 16)
    - Treatment, 1970-1977. (Folder 22: 17)
      Articles, clipping, flyer, newsletter, and related materials
    - Valium (Diazepam), 1971-1975. (Folder 22: 18)
      Letters to the editor and printed matter
    - Youth, 1969-1977. (Folder 22: 19)
      Articles, clipping, newsletter, paper, and related materials
  - Dunn survey, 1963. (Box-folder 23: 1)
  - E. M. Biggers Printer, undated. (Folder 23: 2)
  - East Bay Committee against Flouridation, Berkeley, California, 1963. (Folder 23: 3)
    Information sheet
  - Eastland, James Oliver, 1969. (Folder 23: 4)
  - Eckanar, 1976. (Folder 23: 5)
    Article and pamphlet
  - Ecology, undated. (Folder 23: 6)
  - Economic check-up, 1961. (Folder 23: 7)
  - Economists National Committee on Monetary Policy, 1953. (Folder 23: 8)
    Articles, flyer, and list of recommendations
  - Economic Research Associates, 1958. (Folder 23: 9)
  - Edgar Case Publishing Company, 1961. (Folder 23: 10)
  - Edmondson Economic Service, 1934-1940. (Folder 23: 11)
  - Education for Freedom Foundation, 1961. (Folder 23: 12)
  - Education Information, Inc.
    - Amarillo, Texas, 1960s. (Folder 23: 13)
      Brochures, form letter, and printed matter
    - Omaha, Nebraska, 1965. (Folder 23: 14)
      Research report
    - Fullerton, California, 1950s-1960s. (Folder 23: 15-16)
      Brochure, course outline, form letter, flyer, and miscellany
    - Sacramento, California, 1969-1970. (Folder 23: 17)
  - Educational Reviewer, Inc., undated. (Folder 23: 18)
  - Eichmann, Adolf, 1961. (Folder 23: 19)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1953. (Folder 23: 20)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1952-1957. (Folder 23: 21)
    Address, article, clippings, printed matter, and related materials
  - Electoral college reforms, 1967-1968. (Folder 23: 22)
  - Elks Club, undated. (Folder 23: 23)
  - Elmore County White Citizens Council, Wetumpka, Alabama, 1964-1966. (Folder 23: 24)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, New York, 1959. (Folder 23: 25)
  - Emergency Committee to Defend Liberties of Arizona Public Employees, Tucson, Arizona, 1961-1964. (Folder 23: 26)
    Brochure, printed matter, and miscellany
  - Emergency Fund to Stop Capital Punishment, 1977?. (Folder 23: 27)
  - Encampment for Citizenship, 1958. (Folder 23: 28)
  - Energy Research Corporation, undated. (Folder 23: 29)
  - English, Rachael, 1951. (Folder 23: 30)
  - Episcopal Peace Fellowship, New York, 1965-1967. (Folder 23: 31)
  - Episcopalian Education and Information Council of Florida--"And Should ...," Brunner, Emil, 1961. (Folder 23: 32)
  - Environmental action, 1977. (Folder 23: 33)
  - Environmental Defense Fund, East Setauket, New York, 1973. (Folder 23: 34)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, 1974. (Folder 23: 35)
    Brochure and miscellany
  - Espionage, undated. (Folder 23: 36)
  - Everingham, Harry T., 1962. (Folder 23: 37)
  - Exclusive, Washington, D.C., 1957. (Folder 23: 38)
  - Executive Book Club, Inc., undated. (Folder 23: 39)
  - Executive's Dinner Club of Tucson, Arizona, 1961. (Folder 23: 40)
  - Experimental University, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1973. (Folder 23: 41)
  - Fact Finder, Chicago, Illinois, 1960s. (Folder 23: 42)
  - Fact sheet publication, Los Angeles, 1972. (Folder 23: 43)
  - Fair Employment Practices Commission, New York, undated. (Folder 23: 44)
  - Faith Theological Seminary, 1972-1973. (Folder 23: 45)
    Form letters and remarks
  - Falque, F. C., 1960. (Folder 23: 46)
    Address
  - Farah Strike Support Committee, Berkeley, California, 1973. (Folder 23: 47)
  - Farmers Association, Des Moines, Iowa, 1964. (Folder 23: 48)
  - Farm Workers Boycott Committee, Berkeley, California, 1965. (Folder 23: 49)
  - Fascism, 1962. (Folder 23: 50)
  - Features and News from behind the Iron Curtain, 1962. (Folder 23: 51)
    Letter and miscellany
  - Federal budget, 1957. (Folder 23: 52)
    Clipping and cartoon
  - Federal bureaucracy, 1957. (Folder 23: 53)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, undated. (Folder 23: 54)
  - Federal funding, 1957. (Folder 23: 55)
  - Federal Union, Inc., Washington, D.C., 1955. (Folder 23: 56)
  - Federal wage stabilization, undated. (Folder 23: 57)
  - Water projects (federal), 1950-1964. (Folder 23: 58)
    Brochure, clippings, printed matter, and related materials
  - Federation for Constitutional Government, 1958. (Folder 23: 59)
  - Federation of American Scientists, Washington, D.C., 1965. (Folder 23: 60)
  - Federation of Americans Supporting Science and Technology, undated. (Folder 23: 61)
    Form letter and program
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, New York, 1959. (Folder 23: 62)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation, New York, 1952-1968. (Folder 23: 63)
    Brochures, flyers, printed matter, and related material
  - Female liberation, Berkeley, California, 1972. (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Fifth Amendment--"I Refuse to Answer ...," Smith, Beverly, 1953. (Folder 24: 2)
  - Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, New York, 1967. (Folder 24: 3)
  - Fighting Home Folks of Fighting Men, Glenwood Springs, Colorado, 1954. (Folder 24: 4)
    Flyers and miscellany
  - File of Volunteers for the United States, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1960s. (Folder 24: 5)
  - Films, 1956-1972. (Folder 24: 6)
  - Firearms and individual rights, North Hollywood, California, 1972. (Folder 24: 7)
    Acknowledgement
  - First National Society, 1959. (Folder 24: 8)
    Certificate of membership
  - First World: An International Journal of Black Thought, 1977 (Folder 24: 9)
  - Flett, Austin T., Chicago, Illinois, 1960. (Folder 24: 10)
  - Flick-Reedy Corporation, 1967. (Folder 24: 11)
  - Florida Coalition of Patriotic Societies, Tampa, Florida, 1960. (Folder 24: 12)
  - Florida Minuteman, undated. (Folder 24: 13)
  - Flouridation, 1952-1970. (Folder 24: 14)
    Article, clipping, printed matter, and report
  - For All Comprehensive Truth Committee, Phoenix, Arizona, 1960s. (Folder 24: 15)
  - For America
    - Washington, D.C., 1955-1959. (Folder 24: 16)
      Brochure, flyer, leaflet, letter, notes, report, and miscellany
    - California, Los Angeles, 1959. (Folder 24: 17)
    - Pima County branch, Tucson, Arizona, 1955-1960s. (Folder 24: 18)
      Form letter, list of branch offices, and miscellany
  - Forces of Liberation, New York, 1960s. (Folder 24: 19)
  - Ford Foundation, 1968. (Folder 24: 20)
  - Ford, Gerald, 1977-1978. (Folder 24: 21)
    Letters and five photographic prints depicting President Gerald Ford and First Lady Betty Ford
  - Foreign Policy Association World Affairs Center, New York, 1962. (Folder 24: 22)
  - Foreign student exchange programs, 1964. (Folder 24: 23)
  - Fortune Society, undated. (Folder 24: 24)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Irvington-on-Hudson, New York, 1953-1974. (Folder 24: 25)
    Brochures, memorandum, postcard, and related materials
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 1958-1968. (Folder 24: 26-27)
    Brochures, correspondence, flyers, memorandum, and related materials
  - Foundation for Re-Education, Seattle, Washington, 1951-1970. (Folder 24: 28)
    Pamphlets and miscellany
  - Foundation for Social Research, Los Angeles, California, undated. (Folder 24: 29)
  - Foundation for the Study of Cycles, New York, 1957. (Folder 24: 30)
  - Foundations, 1953. (Folder 24: 31)
    Address, clipping, and printed matter
  - Free Enterprise Institute, Los Angeles, California, 1961. (Folder 24: 32)
  - Free Marketing Council, Salinas, California, 1972. (Folder 24: 33)
  - Free Men Speak, 1955. (Folder 24: 34)
  - Free Press, undated. (Folder 24: 35)
  - Free Tract Society, Inc., undated. (Folder 24: 36)
  - Free Trade Union Committee, 1951. (Folder 24: 37)
    Map
  - Freedom and Peace Party, New York, 1968. (Folder 24: 38)
  - Freedom and union, 1969. (Folder 24: 39)
    Article and press release
  - Freedom Builders of America, Valley Center, California, 1950s. (Folder 24: 40)
  - Freedom Center, Portland, Oregon, 1961. (Folder 24: 41)
  - Freedom Clubs
    - Los Angeles, California, 1955. (Folder 24: 42)
      Brochures and letters
    - Chicago, Illinois, 1960s. (Folder 24: 43)
  - Freedom fighters, 1963. (Folder 24: 44)
    Report and related materials
  - Freedom Forum, Pepperdine College, Los Angeles, California, 1960s. (Folder 24: 45)
  - Freedom Leadership Foundation, Washington, D.C., 1971. (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Freedom, 1963. (Folder 25: 2)
  - Freedom Studies Center, Boston, Virginia, 1971. (Folder 25: 3)
  - Freedom to Read Foundation, Chicago, Illinois, 1973. (Folder 25: 4)
    Brochure, flyer, price list and order form, and statement
  - Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge, Pennsylvania, 1960s. (Folder 25: 5)
    Leaflet, pamphlet, and miscellany
  - Freeman, New York, 1950, 1955. (Folder 25: 6)
    Flyers and pamphlet
  - Freeman Institute, 1976?. (Folder 25: 7)
  - French communists, 1954. (Folder 25: 8)
  - Freud, Sigmund, 1989-1992. (Folder 25: 9)
    Announcement of exhibition tour
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation, Washington, D.C., 1959-1967. (Folder 25: 10)
    Annual report, statement, and related materials
  - Friends of Constitutional Thought, 1956. (Folder 25: 11)
  - Friends of General Walker, Dallas, Texas, 1961-1964. (Folder 25: 12)
  - Friends of Louis F. Budenz, Brighton, Massachusetts, 1957-1962. (Folder 25: 13)
  - Friends of Progressive Labor, Columbia University, New York, 1964. (Folder 25: 14)
  - Friends of Rafferty, Los Angeles, California, 1968. (Folder 25: 15)
  - Friends of Ronald Reagan, undated. (Folder 25: 16)
  - Friends of Rhodesian Independence, Washington, D.C., 1965-1966. (Folder 25: 17)
    Clippings, form letter, and miscellany
  - Friends of the Constitution, 1940. (Folder 25: 18)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1973. (Folder 25: 19)
  - Friend's Peace Committee, undated. (Folder 25: 20)
    Article and leaflet
  - Fundamental American Freedoms, Washington, D.C., 1963. (Folder 25: 21)
  - Fundamental Evangelistic Association, 1972-1973. (Folder 25: 22)
    Brochure, flyers, printed matter, and miscellany
  - Fund for Animals--National Campaign to Save the Dolphin, undated. (Folder 25: 23)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1956. (Folder 25: 24)
  - Gardner, John W., 1970. (Folder 25: 25)
  - Gay rights, 1973. (Folder 25: 26)
    Flyer, printed matter, and miscellany
  - Genocide, 1951-1954. (Folder 25: 27)
    Clipping, flyer, and printed matter
  - Germany, 1972-1983. (Folder 25: 28)
    Clipping, interviews, letter, printed matter, and reports
  - Gilbert, Dan (evangelist), 1956. (Folder 25: 29)
  - Glad Day Press, 1973. (Folder 25: 30)
  - Gold standard, 1956-1957. (Folder 25: 31)
  - Gold Standard League, 1951-1952. (Folder 25: 32)
    Article, bulletin, clipping, invitation, letter, and miscellany
  - Golden Gate budget, 1937. (Folder 25: 33)
  - Goldwater for President Committee 1960s, undated. (Folder 25: 34)
  - Goldwater for 1964, undated. (Folder 25: 35)
  - Gospel Tract Society--"Brotherhood of Man: A Smoke Screen," Hargis, Billy James, undated. (Folder 25: 36)
  - Governmental interference, 1961. (Folder 25: 37)
    Printed matter, record of executive orders, and miscellany
  - Government records, undated. (Folder 25: 38)
  - Government spending, undated. (Folder 25: 39)
  - Grand Central Industrial, undated. (Folder 25: 40)
  - Great Atlantic Radio Conspiracy, 1972-1973. (Folder 25: 41)
    List of titles and printed matter
  - Great Seal of the United States, 1935, 1956.; See also box 19 (Folder 25: 42)
    Clippings and photocopy of the seal.
  - Great Society, 1966. (Folder 25: 43)
  - Greater Cleveland Association of Arab Americans, Cleveland, Ohio, 1970s. (Folder 25: 44)
  - Greater Detroit School of Anti-Communism, 1965. (Folder 25: 45)
  - Greater Miami School of Anti-Communism, 1961. (Folder 25: 46)
  - Greater Nebraskan, 1966. (Folder 25: 47)
    Printed matter and program
  - Greater New York Committee Opposed to Flouridation, New York, 1960s. (Folder 25: 48)
  - Greater Phoenix School of Anti-Communism, 1961. (Folder 25: 49)
    Form letter, list of faculty, and schedule
  - Greene County Civic Coalition Bulletin, West Coxsackie, New York, 1960. (Folder 25: 50)
  - Greenpeace Foundation, undated. (Folder 25: 51)
  - Groseclose, William, and Association, 1965-1967. (Folder 25: 52)
    Letters to the editor
  - Group of Methodists, undated. (Folder 25: 53)
  - Guardians of American Education, 1955. (Folder 25: 54)
    Clipping, list of categories of membership, and miscellany
  - Guardians of our American Heritage, 1947. (Folder 25: 55)
    Message
  - Gun registration controversies, 1960s. (Folder 25: 56)
    Brochure, clipping, flyer, printed matter, and miscellany
  - Guns and Ammo--"The Right to Keep and Bear Arms," Samuels, B. F., 1962. (Folder 25: 57)
  - Hall of Free Enterprise, 1964-1965. (Folder 25: 58)
    Brochure, comments, correspondence, flyer, printed matter, and related materials
  - Hall-Tyner Campaign Committee, 1976. (Folder 25: 59)
    Highlights from a speech
  - Halton, Hugh, 1957. (Folder 25: 60)
    Articles and form letter
  - Hamilton, Barney A., undated. (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Harrisburg Defense Committee, New York, 1970-1971. (Folder 26: 2)
  - Hawaii Foundation for American Freedoms, Inc., Honolulu, Hawaii, 1960s. (Folder 26: 3)
  - Heads Up, San Diego, California, 1960. (Folder 26: 4)
  - Health Professions for McCarthy, New York, 1968. (Folder 26: 5)
  - Health research, 1944. (Folder 26: 6)
  - Henry George School of Social Science, undated. (Folder 26: 7)
    Form letter, printed matter, and questionnaire
  - Heritage Foundation, undated. (Folder 26: 8)
  - Hermann, Rudolf, 1992. (Folder 26: 9)
    Poster and information about exhibit
  - Highlander Center, 1970-1977. (Folder 26: 10)
    Form letter, flyer, and miscellany
  - Highlander Folk School, 1957. (Folder 26: 11)
  - Highlander Research and Education Center, Highlander Folk School, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1972-1973. (Folder 26: 12)
    Brochures, newsletter, printed matter, summary of activities, and related materials
  - Hiroshima House Foundation, New York, 1966. (Folder 26: 13)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1954, 1960. (Folder 26: 14)
  - Hitler, Adolf, 1933-1939. (Folder 26: 15)
    Excerpts from speeches
  - Home buying, 1956-1957. (Folder 26: 16)
  - Honest Dollar Committee, Denver, Colorado, 1964. (Folder 26: 17)
  - Housewives Organized for Better Living, Scottsdale, Arizona, 1966. (Folder 26: 18)
  - Houston 12 Defense Committee, Houston, Texas, 1973. (Folder 26: 19)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1957-1964. (Folder 26: 20-21)
    Address, articles, clipping, printed matter, and remarks
  - Housing, undated. (Folder 26: 22)
  - Hubbard, Bela, Tucson, Arizona, 1952, 1957. (Folder 26: 23)
    List of congressmen and senators, and remarks
  - Human Events, 1959-1962. (Folder 26: 24)
    Form letter, leaflet, newsletter, and related materials
  - Hutley for Mayor Committee, undated. (Folder 26: 25)
  - Iame, Center for Creative Decisions, undated. (Folder 26: 26)
  - Illinois, PTA, Federal Aid to Educators, undated. (Folder 26: 27)
  - Impact films, undated. (Folder 26: 28)
  - Imperial Policy Group, undated. (Folder 26: 29)
    Letter and note
  - Independence Foundation, Inc., undated. (Folder 26: 30)
  - Independent Action, San Jose, California, 1960s. (Folder 26: 31)
  - Independent American, Louisiana, 1958-1970. (Folder 26: 32)
    Announcement, brochures, form letters, and miscellany
  - Independent American, New Orleans, Louisiana, undated. (Folder 26: 33)
  - Independent Board for Presbyterian Foreign Missions, 1972. (Folder 26: 34-35)
  - Independent Committee on Vietnam (ICV) Newsletter, 1967. (Folder 26: 36)
  - Independent Information Center, 1962. (Folder 26: 37)
  - Individuals against the Crime of Silence, Los Angeles, California, 1965. (Folder 26: 38)
    Record of declaration
  - Indochina Resource Center, Washington, D.C., 1969-1973. (Folder 26: 39)
  - Inflation survival letter, undated. (Folder 26: 40)
  - Information Council of the Americas, Washington, D.C., 1968, 1969. (Folder 26: 41)
  - Institute for American Democracy, New York, 1947. (Folder 26: 42)
    Letter, printed matter, and related materials